// data/questions.js
const questions = [


    {
        id: 1,
        question: '1. What is the capital of France?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "maths"

      },
      
      {
        id: 2,
        question: '2. who are you',
        options:[1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 1,

        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "maths"
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: '3. Who painted the Mona Lisa?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 1,

        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "maths"
      },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: '4. What is the currency of Brazil?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,

        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "maths"
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: '5. What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 2,



        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "maths"
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: '6. Who wrote the novel "Pride and Prejudice"?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,

        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "upsc"
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: '7. In which city is the Eiffel Tower located?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: '8. Which artist painted "Starry Night"?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 2,

        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
         type : "upsc"

      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: '9. What is the largest ocean in the world?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 3,

        unseen :true,
        attempted : false,
        pending : true,
        time : 0,
        type : "upsc"
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: '10. Who discovered gravity?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        type : "upsc"
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: '11. Which city hosted the 2016 Summer Olympics?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        type : "iit"
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: '12. Who painted the ceiling of the Sistine Chapel?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        type : "iit"
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: '13. What is the largest animal on Earth?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        type : "iit"
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: '14. Which country is home to the Great Barrier Reef?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        type : "iit"
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: '15. Who is the author of "To Kill a Mockingbird"?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        type : "iit"
      },
      {
        id: 16,
        question: '16. What is the capital of Canada?',
        options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        type : "upsc"
      },
      {
        id: 17,
        question: '17. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
        options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        type : "english"
      },

    // Add more questions here
    {
      id: 18,
      question: '18. What is the capital of Canada?',
      options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      type : "english"
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: '19. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      type : "english"
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: '20. What is the capital of Canada?',
      options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      type : "english"
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: '21. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      type : "english"
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: '22. What is the capital of Canada?',
      options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      type : "maths"
    },
    {
      id: 23,
      question: '23. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      type : "upsc"
    },
    {
      id: 24,
      question: '24. What is the capital of Canada?',
      options:  [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 2,
      type : "iit"
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: '25. Who painted the "Last Supper"?',
      options: [1, 2, 3, 4,5],
      correctAnswer: 1,
      type : "english"
    },









    
    
  ];
  
  export default questions;
  